<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Monitoring KubeDB operator on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v0.13.0-rc.0/setup/monitoring/</link><description>Recent content in Monitoring KubeDB operator on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v0.13.0-rc.0/setup/monitoring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Monitoring KubeDB Operator</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v0.13.0-rc.0/setup/monitoring/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v0.13.0-rc.0/setup/monitoring/overview/</guid><description>Monitoring KubeDB Operator KubeDB has native support for monitoring via Prometheus. You can use builtin Prometheus scraper or CoreOS Prometheus Operator to monitor KubeDB supported databases as well as KubeDB operator itself. This tutorial will show you what metrics KubeDB operator exports and how to enable monitoring for the operator itself.
Overview KubeDB operator pod runs an Extension API Server which self hosts admission webhooks such as MutatingAdmissionWebhook and ValidatingAdmissionWebhook. The extension API server exports some metrics in /metrics path of TLS secured 8443 port.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring KubeDB Operator Using CoreOS Prometheus Operator</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v0.13.0-rc.0/setup/monitoring/coreos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v0.13.0-rc.0/setup/monitoring/coreos/</guid><description>Monitoring KubeDB Operator Using CoreOS Prometheus Operator CoreOS prometheus-operator provides simple and Kubernetes native way to deploy and configure Prometheus server. This tutorial will show you how to use CoreOS Prometheus operator for monitoring KubeDB operator.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster. If you do not already have a cluster, you can create one by using Minikube.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring KubeDB Operator with builtin Prometheus</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v0.13.0-rc.0/setup/monitoring/builtin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v0.13.0-rc.0/setup/monitoring/builtin/</guid><description>Monitoring KubeDB Operator with builtin Prometheus This tutorial will show you how to configure builtin Prometheus scraper to monitor KubeDB operator.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster. If you do not already have a cluster, you can create one by using Minikube.
If you are not familiar with how to configure Prometheus to scrape metrics from various Kubernetes resources, please read the tutorial from here.</description></item></channel></rss>