<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference | KubeDB CLI on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.28/reference/cli/</link><description>Recent content in Reference | KubeDB CLI on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.28/reference/cli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kubectl-Dba</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.28/reference/cli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.28/reference/cli/</guid><description>kubectl-dba kubectl plugin for KubeDB
Synopsis kubectl plugin for KubeDB by AppsCode - Kubernetes ready production-grade Databases
Find more information at https://kubedb.com
kubectl-dba [flags] Options --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups. --cache-dir string Default HTTP cache directory (default &amp;quot;/home/runner/.kube/http-cache&amp;quot;) --certificate-authority string Path to a cert file for the certificate authority --client-certificate string Path to a client certificate file for TLS --client-key string Path to a client key file for TLS --cluster string The name of the kubeconfig cluster to use --context string The name of the kubeconfig context to use --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) -h, --help help for kubectl-dba --insecure-skip-tls-verify If true, the server's certificate will not be checked for validity.</description></item><item><title>Kubectl-Dba Completion</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.28/reference/cli/kubectl-dba_completion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.28/reference/cli/kubectl-dba_completion/</guid><description>kubectl-dba completion Generate completion script
Synopsis To load completions:
Bash:
$ source &amp;lt;(kubectl-dba completion bash)
To load completions for each session, execute once: Linux: $ kubectl-dba completion bash &amp;gt; /etc/bash_completion.d/kubectl-dba MacOS: $ kubectl-dba completion bash &amp;gt; /usr/local/etc/bash_completion.d/kubectl-dba
Zsh:
If shell completion is not already enabled in your environment you will need to enable it. You can execute the following once: $ echo &amp;ldquo;autoload -U compinit; compinit&amp;rdquo; &amp;raquo; ~/.zshrc
To load completions for each session, execute once: $ kubectl-dba completion zsh &amp;gt; &amp;ldquo;${fpath[1]}/_kubectl-dba&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Kubectl-Dba Describe</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.28/reference/cli/kubectl-dba_describe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.28/reference/cli/kubectl-dba_describe/</guid><description>kubectl-dba describe Show details of a specific resource or group of resources
Synopsis Show details of a specific resource or group of resources. This command joins many API calls together to form a detailed description of a given resource or group of resources.
Use &amp;ldquo;kubectl api-resources&amp;rdquo; for a complete list of supported resources.
kubectl-dba describe (-f FILENAME | TYPE [NAME_PREFIX | -l label] | TYPE/NAME) Examples # Describe a elasticsearch kubedb describe elasticsearches elasticsearch-demo # Describe a postgres kubedb describe pg/postgres-demo # Describe all postgreses kubedb describe pg Valid resource types include: * all * etcds * elasticsearches * postgreses * mysqls * mongodbs * redises * memcacheds Options --all-namespaces If present, list the requested object(s) across all namespaces.</description></item><item><title>Kubectl-Dba Version</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.28/reference/cli/kubectl-dba_version/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.28/reference/cli/kubectl-dba_version/</guid><description>kubectl-dba version Prints binary version number.
Synopsis Prints binary version number.
kubectl-dba version [flags] Options --check string Check version constraint -h, --help help for version --short Print just the version number. Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups.</description></item></channel></rss>