<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MySQL on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mysql/</link><description>Recent content in MySQL on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mysql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CLI | KubeDB</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mysql/cli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mysql/cli/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Manage KubeDB objects using CLIs KubeDB CLI KubeDB comes with its own cli. It is called kubedb cli. kubedb can be used to manage any KubeDB object. kubedb cli also performs various validations to improve ux. To install KubeDB cli on your workstation, follow the steps here.
How to Create objects kubectl create creates a database CRD object in default namespace by default.</description></item><item><title>Connecting to a MySQL Cluster</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mysql/clients/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mysql/clients/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Connecting to a MySQL Cluster KubeDB creates separate services for primary and secondary replicas. In this tutorial, we are going to show you how to connect your application with primary or secondary replicas using those services.
Before You Begin Read mysql group replication concept to learn about MySQL Group Replication.
You need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item><item><title>Initialize MySQL using Script</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mysql/initialization/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mysql/initialization/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Initialize MySQL using Script This tutorial will show you how to use KubeDB to initialize a MySQL database with *.sql, *.sh and/or *.sql.gz script. In this tutorial we will use .sql script stored in GitHub repository kubedb/mysql-init-scripts.
Note: The yaml files that are used in this tutorial are stored in docs/guides/mysql/initialization/yamls folder in GitHub repository kubedb/docs.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item><item><title>MySQL</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mysql/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mysql/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Supported MySQL Features Features Availability Clustering ✓ Persistent Volume ✓ Instant Backup ✓ Scheduled Backup ✓ Initialize using Snapshot ✓ Initialize using Script (*.sql, *sql.gz and/or *.sh) ✓ Custom Configuration ✓ Using Custom docker image ✓ Builtin Prometheus Discovery ✓ Using Prometheus operator ✓ Life Cycle of a MySQL Object User Guide Quickstart MySQL with KubeDB Operator.</description></item><item><title>MySQL Quickstart</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mysql/quickstart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mysql/quickstart/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
MySQL QuickStart This tutorial will show you how to use KubeDB to run a MySQL database.
Note: The yaml files used in this tutorial are stored in docs/guides/mysql/quickstart/yamls folder in GitHub repository kubedb/docs.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster. If you do not already have a cluster, you can create one by using kind.</description></item><item><title>Run MySQL using Private Registry</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mysql/private-registry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mysql/private-registry/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Deploy MySQL from private Docker registry KubeDB operator supports using private Docker registry. This tutorial will show you how to use KubeDB to run MySQL database using private Docker images.
Before You Begin Read concept of MySQL Version Catalog to learn detail concepts of MySQLVersion object.
You need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item><item><title>Run MySQL with Custom RBAC resources</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mysql/custom-rbac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mysql/custom-rbac/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Using Custom RBAC resources KubeDB (version 0.13.0 and higher) supports finer user control over role based access permissions provided to a MySQL instance. This tutorial will show you how to use KubeDB to run MySQL instance with custom RBAC resources.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item></channel></rss>