<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Use X-Pack with KubeDB Elasticsearch on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.27-rc.2/guides/elasticsearch/x-pack/</link><description>Recent content in Use X-Pack with KubeDB Elasticsearch on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.27-rc.2/guides/elasticsearch/x-pack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Disable X-Pack</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.27-rc.2/guides/elasticsearch/x-pack/disable-xpack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.27-rc.2/guides/elasticsearch/x-pack/disable-xpack/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Disable X-Pack Plugin You data is precious. Definitely, you will not want to leave your production database unprotected. Hence, KubeDB automates Elasticsearch X-Pack configuration. It provides you authentication, authorization and TLS security. However, you can disable X-Pack security. You have to set spec.disableSecurity field of Elasticsearch object to true.
This tutorial will show you how to disable X-Pack security for Elasticsearch database in KubeDB.</description></item><item><title>Run TLS Secured Elasticsearch</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.27-rc.2/guides/elasticsearch/x-pack/use-tls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.27-rc.2/guides/elasticsearch/x-pack/use-tls/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Run TLS Secured Elasticsearch X-Pack provides facility to secure your Elasticsearch cluster with TLS. By default, KubeDB does not enable TLS security. You have to enable it by setting spec.enableSSL: true. If TLS is enabled, only HTTPS calls are allowed to database server.
This tutorial will show you how to connect with Elasticsearch cluster using certificate when TLS is enabled.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item><item><title>X-Pack Certificate</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.27-rc.2/guides/elasticsearch/x-pack/issue-certificate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.27-rc.2/guides/elasticsearch/x-pack/issue-certificate/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Issue TLS Certificates X-Pack requires certificates to enable TLS. KubeDB creates necessary certificates automatically. However, if you want to use your own certificates, you can provide them through spec.certificateSecret field of Elasticsearch object.
This tutorial will show you how to generate certificates for X-Pack and use them with Elasticsearch database.
In KubeDB Elasticsearch, keystore and truststore files in JKS format are used instead of certificates and private keys in PEM format.</description></item><item><title>X-Pack Configuration</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.27-rc.2/guides/elasticsearch/x-pack/configuration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.10.27-rc.2/guides/elasticsearch/x-pack/configuration/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
X-Pack Configuration X-Pack is an Elastic Stack extension that provides security along with other features. In KubeDB, X-Pack authentication can be used with elasticsearch 6.8 and 7.2+. In this guide, we will show, how to use xpack authentication or disable it.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item></channel></rss>