<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Using Search Guard with Elasticsearch on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.9.0-rc.0/guides/elasticsearch/search-guard/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Using Search Guard with Elasticsearch on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/0.9.0-rc.0/guides/elasticsearch/search-guard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Disable Search Guard</title>
      <link>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.9.0-rc.0/guides/elasticsearch/search-guard/disable-searchguard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.9.0-rc.0/guides/elasticsearch/search-guard/disable-searchguard/</guid>
      <description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
 Disable Search Guard Plugin Databases are precious. Definitely, you will not want to left your production database unprotected. Hence, KubeDB ship with Search Guard plugin integrated with it. It provides you authentication, authorization and TLS security. However, you can disable Search Guard plugin. You have to set spec.authPlugin field of Elasticsearch object to None.
This tutorial will show you how to disable Search Guard plugin for Elasticsearch database in KubeDB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run TLS Secured Elasticsearch</title>
      <link>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.9.0-rc.0/guides/elasticsearch/search-guard/use-tls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.9.0-rc.0/guides/elasticsearch/search-guard/use-tls/</guid>
      <description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
 Run TLS Secured Elasticsearch Search Guard provides facility to secure your Elasticsearch cluster with TLS. By default, KubeDB does not enable TLS security. You have to enable it by setting spec.enableSSL: true. If TLS is enabled, only HTTPS calls are allowed to database server.
This tutorial will show you how to connect with Elasticsearch cluster using certificate when TLS is enabled.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Guard</title>
      <link>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.9.0-rc.0/guides/elasticsearch/search-guard/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.9.0-rc.0/guides/elasticsearch/search-guard/overview/</guid>
      <description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
 Search Guard Search Guard(®) is an Elasticsearch plugin that offers encryption, authentication, and authorization. It supports fine grained role-based access control to clusters, indices, documents and fields.
 Search Guard authenticates the credentials against the configured authentication backend(s). Search Guard authorizes the user by retrieving a list of the user’s roles from the configured authorization backend  TLS certificates Search Guard relies heavily on the use of TLS, both for the REST and the transport layer of Elasticsearch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Guard Certificate</title>
      <link>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.9.0-rc.0/guides/elasticsearch/search-guard/issue-certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.9.0-rc.0/guides/elasticsearch/search-guard/issue-certificate/</guid>
      <description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
 Issue TLS Certificates Search Guard requires certificates to enable TLS. KubeDB creates necessary certificates automatically. However, if you want to use your own certificates, you can provide them through spec.certificateSecret field of Elasticsearch object.
This tutorial will show you how to generate certificates for Search Guard and use them with Elasticsearch database.
In KubeDB Elasticsearch, keystore and truststore files in JKS format are used instead of certificates and private keys in PEM format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Guard Configuration</title>
      <link>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.9.0-rc.0/guides/elasticsearch/search-guard/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.9.0-rc.0/guides/elasticsearch/search-guard/configuration/</guid>
      <description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
 Search Guard Configuration Search Guard configuration enables basic flow as follows:
 Search Guard authenticates the credentials against the configured authentication backend(s). Search Guard authorizes the user by retrieving a list of the user’s roles from the configured authorization backend  Roles retrieved from authorization backends are called backend roles.   Search Guard maps the user and backend roles to Search Guard roles.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>