<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Horizontal Scaling on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.12.10/guides/mongodb/scaling/horizontal-scaling/</link><description>Recent content in Horizontal Scaling on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.12.10/guides/mongodb/scaling/horizontal-scaling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Horizontal Scaling MongoDB Replicaset</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.12.10/guides/mongodb/scaling/horizontal-scaling/replicaset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.12.10/guides/mongodb/scaling/horizontal-scaling/replicaset/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Horizontal Scale MongoDB Replicaset This guide will show you how to use KubeDB Enterprise operator to scale the replicaset of a MongoDB database.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item><item><title>Horizontal Scaling MongoDB Shard</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.12.10/guides/mongodb/scaling/horizontal-scaling/sharding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.12.10/guides/mongodb/scaling/horizontal-scaling/sharding/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Horizontal Scale MongoDB Shard This guide will show you how to use KubeDB Enterprise operator to scale the shard of a MongoDB database.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item><item><title>MongoDB Horizontal Scaling Overview</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.12.10/guides/mongodb/scaling/horizontal-scaling/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.12.10/guides/mongodb/scaling/horizontal-scaling/overview/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. MongoDB Horizontal Scaling This guide will give an overview on how KubeDB Enterprise operator scales up or down MongoDB database replicas of various component such as ReplicaSet, Shard, ConfigServer, Mongos, etc.
Before You Begin You should be familiar with the following KubeDB concepts: MongoDB MongoDBOpsRequest How Horizontal Scaling Process Works The following diagram shows how KubeDB Enterprise operator scales up or down MongoDB database components.</description></item></channel></rss>