<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ProxySQL Concepts on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/proxysql/concepts/</link><description>Recent content in ProxySQL Concepts on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/proxysql/concepts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AppBinding CRD</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/proxysql/concepts/appbinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/proxysql/concepts/appbinding/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
AppBinding What is AppBinding An AppBinding is a Kubernetes CustomResourceDefinition(CRD) which points to an application using either its URL (usually for a non-Kubernetes resident service instance) or a Kubernetes service object (if self-hosted in a Kubernetes cluster), some optional parameters and a credential secret. To learn more about AppBinding and the problems it solves, please read this blog post: The case for AppBinding.</description></item><item><title>ProxySQL CRD</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/proxysql/concepts/proxysql/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/proxysql/concepts/proxysql/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. ProxySQL What is ProxySQL ProxySQL is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definitions (CRD). It provides declarative configuration for ProxySQL in a Kubernetes native way. You only need to describe the desired configurations in a ProxySQL object, and the KubeDB operator will create Kubernetes objects in the desired state for you.</description></item><item><title>ProxySQLVersion CRD</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/proxysql/concepts/catalog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/proxysql/concepts/catalog/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. ProxySQLVersion What is ProxySQLVersion ProxySQLVersion is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definitions (CRD). It provides a declarative configuration to specify the docker images to be used for ProxySQL deployed with KubeDB in a Kubernetes native way.
When you install KubeDB, a ProxySQLVersion custom resource will be created automatically for supported ProxySQL versions.</description></item></channel></rss>