<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Elasticsearch Snapshotting on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/guides/elasticsearch/snapshot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Elasticsearch Snapshotting on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/guides/elasticsearch/snapshot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Instant Backup of Elasticsearch</title>
      <link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/guides/elasticsearch/snapshot/instant_backup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/guides/elasticsearch/snapshot/instant_backup/</guid>
      <description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
 KubeDB Snapshot KubeDB operator maintains another Custom Resource Definition (CRD) for database backups called Snapshot. Snapshot object is used to take backup or restore from a backup.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster. If you do not already have a cluster, you can create one by using Minikube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scheduled Backup of Elasticsearch</title>
      <link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/guides/elasticsearch/snapshot/scheduled_backup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/guides/elasticsearch/snapshot/scheduled_backup/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t know how backup works? Check tutorial on Instant Backup.
 Database Scheduled Snapshots KubeDB supports taking periodic backups for Elasticsearch database.
Before you begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster. If you do not already have a cluster, you can create one by using Minikube.
Now, install KubeDB cli on your workstation and KubeDB operator in your cluster following the steps here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>