<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Concepts on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.10.0/concepts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Concepts on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/0.10.0/concepts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Concepts | KubeDB</title>
      <link>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.10.0/concepts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.10.0/concepts/</guid>
      <description>Concepts Concepts help you learn about the different parts of the KubeDB and the abstractions it uses.
 What is KubeDB  Overview. Provides a conceptual introduction to KubeDB, including the problems it solves and its high-level architecture.   Databases  Elasticsearch. Introduces the concept of Elasticsearch to manage Elasticsearch using KubeDB. Memcached. Introduces the concept of Memcached to manage Memcached using KubeDB. MongoDB. Introduces the concept of MongoDB to manage MongoDB using KubeDB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snapshot</title>
      <link>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.10.0/concepts/snapshot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.10.0/concepts/snapshot/</guid>
      <description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
 Snapshot What is Snapshot A Snapshot is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definitions (CRD). It provides declarative configuration for database snapshots in a Kubernetes native way. You only need to describe the desired backup behavior in a Snapshot object. KubeDB operator will launch a Job to perform backup operation. Once the snapshot process is complete, it uploads the snapshot data to various cloud providers S3, GCS, Azure, OpenStack Swift and/or locally mounted volumes using osm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>