<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Compute Autoscaling on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/elasticsearch/autoscaler/compute/</link><description>Recent content in Compute Autoscaling on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/elasticsearch/autoscaler/compute/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Elasticsearch Combined Cluster Autoscaling</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/elasticsearch/autoscaler/compute/combined/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/elasticsearch/autoscaler/compute/combined/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Autoscaling the Compute Resource of an Elasticsearch Combined Cluster This guide will show you how to use KubeDB to autoscale compute resources i.e. cpu and memory of an Elasticsearch combined cluster.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item><item><title>Elasticsearch Compute Autoscaling Overview</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/elasticsearch/autoscaler/compute/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/elasticsearch/autoscaler/compute/overview/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Elasticsearch Compute Resource Autoscaling This guide will give an overview on how the KubeDB Autoscaler operator autoscales the database compute resources i.e. cpu and memory using elasticsearchautoscaler crd.
Before You Begin You should be familiar with the following KubeDB concepts: Elasticsearch ElasticsearchAutoscaler ElasticsearchOpsRequest How Compute Autoscaling Works The Auto Scaling process consists of the following steps:</description></item><item><title>Elasticsearch Topology Cluster Autoscaling</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/elasticsearch/autoscaler/compute/topology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/elasticsearch/autoscaler/compute/topology/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Autoscaling the Compute Resource of an Elasticsearch Topology Cluster This guide will show you how to use KubeDB to autoscale compute resources i.e. cpu and memory of an Elasticsearch topology cluster.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item></channel></rss>