<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>KubeDB on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.11.0/</link><description>Recent content in KubeDB on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.11.0/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contributing | KubeDB</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.11.0/welcome/contributing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.11.0/welcome/contributing/</guid><description>Contribution Guidelines Want to hack on KubeDB?
AppsCode projects are Apache 2.0 licensed and accept contributions via GitHub pull requests. This document outlines some of the conventions on development workflow, commit message formatting, contact points and other resources to make it easier to get your contribution accepted.
Certificate of Origin By contributing to this project you agree to the Developer Certificate of Origin (DCO). This document was created by the Linux Kernel community and is a simple statement that you, as a contributor, have the legal right to make the contribution.</description></item><item><title>Project Status | KubeDB</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.11.0/welcome/status/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.11.0/welcome/status/</guid><description> Project Status Versioning Policy There are 2 parts to versioning policy:
Operator &amp;amp; cli version: KubeDB follows semver versioning policy. Until 1.0 release is done, there might be breaking changes between point releases of the operator. Please always check the release notes for upgrade instructions. CRD version: kubedb.com/v1alpha1 is considered in alpha. This means breaking changes to the YAML format might happen among different releases of the operator.</description></item><item><title>Support | KubeDB</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.11.0/welcome/support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.11.0/welcome/support/</guid><description>Support We use Slack for public discussions. To chit chat with us or the rest of the community, join us in the Kubernetes Slack team channel #kubedb. To sign up, use our Slack inviter.
To receive product announcements, please join our mailing list or follow us on Twitter. Our mailing list is also used to share design docs shared via Google docs.
If you have found a bug with KubeDB or want to request for new features, please file an issue.</description></item><item><title>Welcome | KubeDB</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.11.0/welcome/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.11.0/welcome/</guid><description>Welcome From here you can learn all about KubeDB&amp;rsquo;s architecture and how to deploy and use KubeDB.
Concepts. Concepts explain some significant aspect of KubeDB. This is where you can learn about what KubeDB does and how it does it.
Setup. Setup contains instructions for installing the KubeDB in various cloud providers.
Guides. Guides show you how to perform tasks with KubeDB.
Reference. Detailed exhaustive lists of command-line options, configuration options, API definitions, and procedures.</description></item></channel></rss>