<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Monitoring Memcached on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.26/guides/memcached/monitoring/</link><description>Recent content in Monitoring Memcached on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.26/guides/memcached/monitoring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Memcached Monitoring Overview</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.26/guides/memcached/monitoring/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.26/guides/memcached/monitoring/overview/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Monitoring Memcached with KubeDB KubeDB has native support for monitoring via Prometheus. You can use builtin Prometheus scraper or Prometheus operator to monitor KubeDB managed databases. This tutorial will show you how database monitoring works with KubeDB and how to configure Database crd to enable monitoring.
Overview KubeDB uses Prometheus exporter images to export Prometheus metrics for respective databases. Following diagram shows the logical flow of database monitoring with KubeDB.</description></item><item><title>Monitor Memcached using Builtin Prometheus Discovery</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.26/guides/memcached/monitoring/using-builtin-prometheus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.26/guides/memcached/monitoring/using-builtin-prometheus/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Monitoring Memcached with builtin Prometheus This tutorial will show you how to monitor Memcached server using builtin Prometheus scraper.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster. If you do not already have a cluster, you can create one by using kind.
Install KubeDB operator in your cluster following the steps here.</description></item><item><title>Monitor Memcached using Prometheus Operator</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.26/guides/memcached/monitoring/using-prometheus-operator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.26/guides/memcached/monitoring/using-prometheus-operator/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Monitoring Memcached Using Prometheus operator Prometheus operator provides simple and Kubernetes native way to deploy and configure Prometheus server. This tutorial will show you how to use Prometheus operator to monitor Memcached server deployed with KubeDB.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item></channel></rss>