<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Setup | KubeDB on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.15/setup/</link><description>Recent content in Setup | KubeDB on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.15/setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setup | KubeDB</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.15/setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.15/setup/</guid><description>Setup Install Community Edition Try Enterprise Edition Compare Editions The setup section contains instructions for installing the KubeDB and its various components in Kubernetes. This section has been divided into the following sub-sections:
Install KubeDB: Installation instructions for KubeDB and its various components. Community Edition: Installation instructions for KubeDB Community Edition. Enterprise Edition: Installation instructions for KubeDB Enterprise Edition. KubeDB kubectl Plugin: Installation instructions for KubeDB kubectl plugin.</description></item><item><title>Upgrade | KubeDB</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.15/setup/upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.15/setup/upgrade/</guid><description>Upgrading KubeDB This guide will show you how to upgrade KubeDB operator. Here, we are going to show how to update the license and how to upgrade between two KubeDB versions.
Updating License KubeDB support updating license without requiring any re-installation or restart. KubeDB creates a Secret named &amp;lt;helm release name&amp;gt;-license with the license file. You just need to update the Secret. The changes will propagate automatically to the operator and it will use the updated license going forward.</description></item></channel></rss>