<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Installation Guide | KubeDB on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.02-rc.0/setup/install/</link><description>Recent content in Installation Guide | KubeDB on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.02-rc.0/setup/install/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Install KubeDB Community Edition</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.02-rc.0/setup/install/community/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.02-rc.0/setup/install/community/</guid><description>Install KubeDB Community Edition KubeDB Community edition is available under AppsCode-Community-1.0.0 license and free to use for both commercial and non-commercial purposes. It comes with the cluster provisioning functionalities. However, it lacks some advanced features such as database backup/recovery, upgrading version, horizontal and vertical scaling, TLS/SSL support via cert-manager, updating configuration post provisioning, connection pooling, etc. compared to the Enterprise edition. A full features comparison between the KubeDB Community edition and Enterprise edition can be found here.</description></item><item><title>Install KubeDB Enterprise Edition</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.02-rc.0/setup/install/enterprise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.02-rc.0/setup/install/enterprise/</guid><description>Install KubeDB Enterprise Edition KubeDB Enterprise edition is the open core version of KubeDB. It includes all the features (clustering, etc.) of KubeDB Community Edition and extends it by automating Day 2 operations, improving security and productivity.
Back and recovery - KubeDB will provide backup &amp;amp; recovery of databases using Stash. Upgrade and Scaling - KubeDB will provide operator managed human-in-the-loop patch and minor upgrade, downgrade and scaling operations SSL Support - KubeDB Enterprise operator supports SSL certificate management for supported database types via Jetstack’s cert-manager project.</description></item><item><title>Install KubeDB kubectl Plugin</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.02-rc.0/setup/install/kubectl_plugin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.02-rc.0/setup/install/kubectl_plugin/</guid><description>Install KubeDB kubectl Plugin KubeDB provides a kubectl plugin to interact with KubeDB resources.
Install using Krew KubeDB kubectl plugin can be installed using Krew. Krew is the plugin manager for kubectl command-line tool. To install follow the steps below:
Install krew following the steps here.
If you have already installed krew, please upgrade krew to version v0.4.0 or later so that you can use custom plugin indexes.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting KubeDB Installation</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.02-rc.0/setup/install/troubleshoting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.01.02-rc.0/setup/install/troubleshoting/</guid><description>Installing in GKE Cluster If you are installing KubeDB on a GKE cluster, you will need cluster admin permissions to install KubeDB operator. Run the following command to grant admin permision to the cluster.
$ kubectl create clusterrolebinding &amp;#34;cluster-admin-$(whoami)&amp;#34; \ --clusterrole=cluster-admin \ --user=&amp;#34;$(gcloud config get-value core/account)&amp;#34; In addition, if your GKE cluster is a private cluster, you will need to either add an additional firewall rule that allows master nodes access port 8443/tcp on worker nodes, or change the existing rule that allows access to ports 443/tcp and 10250/tcp to also allow access to port 8443/tcp.</description></item></channel></rss>