<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Run Elasticsearch with Custom Configuration on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/elasticsearch/configuration/</link><description>Recent content in Run Elasticsearch with Custom Configuration on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/elasticsearch/configuration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configuring Elasticsearch Combined Cluster</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/elasticsearch/configuration/combined-cluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/elasticsearch/configuration/combined-cluster/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Configure Elasticsearch Combined Cluster In Elasticsearch combined cluster, every node can perform as master, data, and ingest nodes simultaneously. In this tutorial, we will see how to configure a combined cluster.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster. If you do not already have a cluster, you can create one by using kind.</description></item><item><title>Configuring Elasticsearch Topology Cluster</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/elasticsearch/configuration/topology-cluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/elasticsearch/configuration/topology-cluster/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Configure Elasticsearch Topology Cluster In an Elasticsearch topology cluster, each node is assigned with a dedicated role such as master, data, and ingest. The cluster must have at least one master node, one data node, and one ingest node. In this tutorial, we will see how to configure a topology cluster.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item><item><title>Run Elasticsearch with Custom Configuration</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/elasticsearch/configuration/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/elasticsearch/configuration/overview/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Elasticsearch with Custom Configuration Files The KubeDB operator allows a user to deploy an Elasticsearch cluster with custom configuration files. The operator also allows the user to configure the security plugins such as X-Pack, SearchGurad, and OpenDistro. If the custom configuration files are not provided, the operator will start the cluster with default configurations.
Overview Elasticsearch has three configuration files:
elasticsearch.yml: for configuring Elasticsearch jvm.</description></item></channel></rss>