<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Compute Autoscaling on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mongodb/autoscaler/compute/</link><description>Recent content in Compute Autoscaling on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mongodb/autoscaler/compute/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MongoDB Compute Autoscaling Overview</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mongodb/autoscaler/compute/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mongodb/autoscaler/compute/overview/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. MongoDB Compute Resource Autoscaling This guide will give an overview on how KubeDB Autoscaler operator autoscales the database compute resources i.e. cpu and memory using mongodbautoscaler crd.
Before You Begin You should be familiar with the following KubeDB concepts: MongoDB MongoDBAutoscaler MongoDBOpsRequest How Compute Autoscaling Works The following diagram shows how KubeDB Autoscaler operator autoscales the resources of MongoDB database components.</description></item><item><title>MongoDB Replicaset Autoscaling</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mongodb/autoscaler/compute/replicaset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mongodb/autoscaler/compute/replicaset/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Autoscaling the Compute Resource of a MongoDB Replicaset Database This guide will show you how to use KubeDB to autoscale compute resources i.e. cpu and memory of a MongoDB replicaset database.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item><item><title>MongoDB Shard Autoscaling</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mongodb/autoscaler/compute/sharding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mongodb/autoscaler/compute/sharding/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Autoscaling the Compute Resource of a MongoDB Sharded Database This guide will show you how to use KubeDB to autoscale compute resources i.e. cpu and memory of a MongoDB sharded database.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item><item><title>MongoDB Standalone Autoscaling</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mongodb/autoscaler/compute/standalone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.04.16/guides/mongodb/autoscaler/compute/standalone/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Autoscaling the Compute Resource of a MongoDB Standalone Database This guide will show you how to use KubeDB to autoscale compute resources i.e. cpu and memory of a MongoDB standalone database.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item></channel></rss>