<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reference on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reference on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubedb</title>
      <link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb/</guid>
      <description>kubedb Command line interface for KubeDB
Synopsis KubeDB by AppsCode - Kubernetes ready production-grade Databases
Find more information at https://github.com/kubedb/cli.
kubedb [flags]  Options  --analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) -h, --help help for kubedb --kube-context string name of the kubeconfig context to use  SEE ALSO  kubedb compare - Compare summary reports kubedb create - Create a resource by filename or stdin kubedb delete - Delete resources by filenames, stdin, resources and names, or by resources and label selector kubedb describe - Show details of a specific resource or group of resources kubedb edit - Edit a resource on the server kubedb get - Display one or many resources kubedb summarize - Export summary report kubedb version - Prints binary version number.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubedb Compare</title>
      <link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb_compare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb_compare/</guid>
      <description> kubedb compare Compare summary reports
Synopsis Compare summary reports
kubedb compare [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for compare --output string Directory used to store summary report --show If true, comparison result will be printed. (default true)  Options inherited from parent commands  --analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --kube-context string name of the kubeconfig context to use  SEE ALSO  kubedb - Command line interface for KubeDB  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubedb Create</title>
      <link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb_create/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb_create/</guid>
      <description>kubedb create Create a resource by filename or stdin
Synopsis Create a resource by filename or stdin.
JSON and YAML formats are accepted.
kubedb create [flags]  Examples  # Create a elasticsearch using the data in elastic.json. kubedb create -f ./elastic.json # Create a elasticsearch based on the JSON passed into stdin. cat elastic.json | kubedb create -f -  Options  -f, --filename stringSlice Filename to use to create the resource -h, --help help for create -n, --namespace string Create object(s) in this namespace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubedb Delete</title>
      <link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb_delete/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb_delete/</guid>
      <description>kubedb delete Delete resources by filenames, stdin, resources and names, or by resources and label selector
Synopsis Delete resources by filenames, stdin, resources and names, or by resources and label selector. JSON and YAML formats are accepted.
Note that the delete command does NOT do resource version checks
kubedb delete ([-f FILENAME] | TYPE [(NAME | -l label | --all)]) [flags]  Examples  # Delete a elasticsearch using the type and name specified in elastic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubedb Describe</title>
      <link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb_describe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb_describe/</guid>
      <description>kubedb describe Show details of a specific resource or group of resources
Synopsis Show details of a specific resource or group of resources. This command joins many API calls together to form a detailed description of a given resource or group of resources.Valid resource types include:
 all
 elasticsearches
 postgreses
 mysqls
 mongodbs
 redises
 memcacheds
 snapshots
 dormantdatabases  kubedb describe (TYPE [NAME_PREFIX] | TYPE/NAME) [flags]  Examples  # Describe a elasticsearch kubedb describe elasticsearches elasticsearch-demo # Describe a postgres kubedb describe pg/postgres-demo # Describe all dormantdatabases kubedb describe drmn  Options  --all-namespaces If present, describe the requested object(s) across all namespaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubedb Edit</title>
      <link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb_edit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb_edit/</guid>
      <description>kubedb edit Edit a resource on the server
Synopsis Edit a resource from the default editor.
The edit command allows you to directly edit any API resource you can retrieve via the command line tools. It will open the editor defined by your KUBEDB _EDITOR, or EDITOR environment variables, or fall back to &amp;lsquo;nano&amp;rsquo;
kubedb edit (RESOURCE/NAME) [flags]  Examples  # Edit the elasticsearch named &#39;elasticsearch-demo&#39;: kubedb edit es/elasticsearch-demo # Use an alternative editor KUBEDB_EDITOR=&amp;quot;nano&amp;quot; kubedb edit es/elasticsearch-demo  Options  -h, --help help for edit -n, --namespace string Edit object(s) in this namespace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubedb Get</title>
      <link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb_get/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb_get/</guid>
      <description>kubedb get Display one or many resources
Synopsis Display one or many resources.
Valid resource types include:
 all
 elasticsearches
 postgreses
 mysqls
 mongodbs
 redises
 memcacheds
 snapshots
 dormantdatabases  kubedb get [flags]  Examples  # List all elasticsearch in ps output format. kubedb get es # List all elasticsearch in ps output format with more information (such as version). kubedb get elasticsearches -o wide # List a single postgres with specified NAME in ps output format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubedb Summarize</title>
      <link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb_summarize/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb_summarize/</guid>
      <description> kubedb summarize Export summary report
Synopsis Export summary report
kubedb summarize [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for summarize --index string Export summary report for this only. -n, --namespace string Export summary report of the requested object from this namespace. (default &amp;quot;default&amp;quot;) --operator-namespace string Name of namespace where operator is running (default &amp;quot;kube-system&amp;quot;) --output string Directory used to store summary report  Options inherited from parent commands  --analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --kube-context string name of the kubeconfig context to use  SEE ALSO  kubedb - Command line interface for KubeDB  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubedb Version</title>
      <link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb_version/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.firebaseapp.com/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/reference/kubedb_version/</guid>
      <description> kubedb version Prints binary version number.
Synopsis Prints binary version number.
kubedb version [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for version  Options inherited from parent commands  --analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --kube-context string name of the kubeconfig context to use  SEE ALSO  kubedb - Command line interface for KubeDB  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>