<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Guides on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.8.0-beta.0/guides/</link><description>Recent content in Guides on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.8.0-beta.0/guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CLI | KubeDB</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.8.0-beta.0/guides/cli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.8.0-beta.0/guides/cli/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Manage KubeDB objects using CLIs KubeDB CLI KubeDB comes with its own cli. It is called kubedb cli. kubedb can be used to deploy KubeDB operator in a cluster and manage all KubeDB objects. kubedb cli also performs various validations to improve ux. To install KubeDB cli on your workstation, follow the steps here.
How to Create objects kubedb create creates a database CRD object in default namespace by default.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.8.0-beta.0/guides/monitoring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.8.0-beta.0/guides/monitoring/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Using Prometheus with KubeDB This tutorial will show you how to monitor KubeDB databases using Prometheus via CoreOS Prometheus Operator.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster. If you do not already have a cluster, you can create one by using Minikube.
Now, install KubeDB cli on your workstation and KubeDB operator in your cluster following the steps here.</description></item><item><title>RBAC</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.8.0-beta.0/guides/rbac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.8.0-beta.0/guides/rbac/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Using RBAC with KubeDB This tutorial will show you how to use KubeDB in a RBAC enabled cluster.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a RBAC enabled Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster. If you do not already have a cluster, you can create one by using Minikube. To create a RBAC enabled cluster using MiniKube, follow the instructions below:</description></item><item><title>Tutorials | KubeDB</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.8.0-beta.0/guides/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.8.0-beta.0/guides/</guid><description>Tutorials This section contains tutorials on how to use KubeDB. Please visit the links below to learn more:
Running PostgreSQL: This tutorial will show you how to use KubeDB to run a PostgreSQL database.
Running Elasticsearch: This tutorial will show you how to use KubeDB to run an Elasticsearch database.
Running MySQL: This tutorial will show you how to use KubeDB to run a MySQL database.</description></item></channel></rss>