<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference | KubeDB Operator on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.07.10-beta.0/reference/operator/</link><description>Recent content in Reference | KubeDB Operator on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.07.10-beta.0/reference/operator/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kubedb-Operator</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.07.10-beta.0/reference/operator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.07.10-beta.0/reference/operator/</guid><description>kubedb-operator KubeDB operator by AppsCode
Synopsis KubeDB operator by AppsCode
Options --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --bypass-validating-webhook-xray if true, bypasses validating webhook xray checks --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) -h, --help help for kubedb-operator --log-flush-frequency duration Maximum number of seconds between log flushes (default 5s) --log_backtrace_at traceLocation when logging hits line file:N, emit a stack trace (default :0) --log_dir string If non-empty, write log files in this directory --logtostderr log to standard error instead of files (default true) --stderrthreshold severity logs at or above this threshold go to stderr --use-kubeapiserver-fqdn-for-aks if true, uses kube-apiserver FQDN for AKS cluster to workaround https://github.</description></item><item><title>Kubedb-Operator Run</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.07.10-beta.0/reference/operator/kubedb-operator_run/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.07.10-beta.0/reference/operator/kubedb-operator_run/</guid><description>kubedb-operator run Run kubedb operator in Kubernetes
Synopsis Run kubedb operator in Kubernetes
kubedb-operator run [flags] Options --audit-dynamic-configuration Enables dynamic audit configuration. This feature also requires the DynamicAuditing feature flag --audit-log-batch-buffer-size int The size of the buffer to store events before batching and writing. Only used in batch mode. (default 10000) --audit-log-batch-max-size int The maximum size of a batch. Only used in batch mode. (default 1) --audit-log-batch-max-wait duration The amount of time to wait before force writing the batch that hadn't reached the max size.</description></item><item><title>Kubedb-Operator Version</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.07.10-beta.0/reference/operator/kubedb-operator_version/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.07.10-beta.0/reference/operator/kubedb-operator_version/</guid><description>kubedb-operator version Prints binary version number.
Synopsis Prints binary version number.
kubedb-operator version [flags] Options --check string Check version constraint -h, --help help for version --short Print just the version number. Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --bypass-validating-webhook-xray if true, bypasses validating webhook xray checks --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --log-flush-frequency duration Maximum number of seconds between log flushes (default 5s) --log_backtrace_at traceLocation when logging hits line file:N, emit a stack trace (default :0) --log_dir string If non-empty, write log files in this directory --logtostderr log to standard error instead of files (default true) --stderrthreshold severity logs at or above this threshold go to stderr --use-kubeapiserver-fqdn-for-aks if true, uses kube-apiserver FQDN for AKS cluster to workaround https://github.</description></item></channel></rss>