<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PostgreSQL Quickstart on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.11.0/guides/postgres/quickstart/</link><description>Recent content in PostgreSQL Quickstart on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/0.11.0/guides/postgres/quickstart/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PostgreSQL Quickstart</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.11.0/guides/postgres/quickstart/quickstart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.11.0/guides/postgres/quickstart/quickstart/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Running PostgreSQL This tutorial will show you how to use KubeDB to run a PostgreSQL database.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster. If you do not already have a cluster, you can create one by using minikube.
Now, install KubeDB cli on your workstation and KubeDB operator in your cluster following the steps here.</description></item><item><title>RBAC for PostgreSQL</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.11.0/guides/postgres/quickstart/rbac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/0.11.0/guides/postgres/quickstart/rbac/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
RBAC Permissions for Postgres If RBAC is enabled in clusters, some PostgreSQL specific RBAC permissions are required. These permissions are required for Leader Election process of PostgreSQL clustering.
Here is the list of additional permissions required by StatefulSet of Postgres:
Kubernetes Resource Resource Names Permission required statefulsets {postgres-name} get pods list, patch configmaps create configmaps {postgres-name}-leader-lock get, update Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item></channel></rss>