<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Horizontal Scaling on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.11.11/guides/mysql/scaling/horizontal-scaling/</link><description>Recent content in Horizontal Scaling on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.11.11/guides/mysql/scaling/horizontal-scaling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Horizontal Scaling MySQL group replication</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.11.11/guides/mysql/scaling/horizontal-scaling/group_replication/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.11.11/guides/mysql/scaling/horizontal-scaling/group_replication/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Horizontal Scale MySQL Group Replication This guide will show you how to use KubeDB enterprise operator to increase/decrease the number of members of a MySQL Group Replication.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item><item><title>MySQL Horizontal Scaling Overview</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.11.11/guides/mysql/scaling/horizontal-scaling/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2020.11.11/guides/mysql/scaling/horizontal-scaling/overview/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Horizontal Scaling Overview This guide will give you an overview of how KubeDB enterprise operator scales up/down the number of members of a MySQL group replication.
Before You Begin You should be familiar with the following KubeDB concepts: MySQL MySQLOpsRequest How Horizontal Scaling Process Works The following diagram shows how KubeDB enterprise operator used to scale up the number of members of a MySQL group replication.</description></item></channel></rss>