<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Legacy Installation Guide | KubeDB on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/setup/legacy-install/</link><description>Recent content in Legacy Installation Guide | KubeDB on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/setup/legacy-install/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Install KubeDB Community Edition</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/setup/legacy-install/community/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/setup/legacy-install/community/</guid><description>Install KubeDB Community Edition KubeDB Community edition is available under AppsCode-Community-1.0.0 license and free to use for both commercial and non-commercial purposes. It comes with the cluster provisioning functionalities. However, it lacks some advanced features such as database backup/recovery, upgrading version, horizontal and vertical scaling, TLS/SSL support via cert-manager, updating configuration post provisioning, connection pooling, etc. compared to the Enterprise edition. A full features comparison between the KubeDB Community edition and Enterprise edition can be found here.</description></item><item><title>Install KubeDB Enterprise Edition</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/setup/legacy-install/enterprise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/setup/legacy-install/enterprise/</guid><description>Install KubeDB Enterprise Edition KubeDB Enterprise edition is the open core version of KubeDB. It includes all the features (clustering, etc.) of KubeDB Community Edition and extends it by automating Day 2 operations, improving security and productivity.
Back and recovery - KubeDB will provide backup &amp;amp; recovery of databases using Stash. Upgrade and Scaling - KubeDB will provide operator managed human-in-the-loop patch and minor upgrade, downgrade and scaling operations SSL Support - KubeDB Enterprise operator supports SSL certificate management for supported database types via Jetstack’s cert-manager project.</description></item></channel></rss>