<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kubedb</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/kubedb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/kubedb/</guid><description>kubedb Command line interface for KubeDB
Synopsis KubeDB by AppsCode - Kubernetes ready production-grade Databases
Find more information at https://github.com/kubedb/cli.
kubedb [flags] Options --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups. --cache-dir string Default HTTP cache directory (default &amp;quot;/home/tamal/.</description></item><item><title>Kubedb Api-Resources</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/kubedb_api-resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/kubedb_api-resources/</guid><description>kubedb api-resources Print the supported API resources on the server
Synopsis Print the supported API resources on the server
kubedb api-resources [flags] Examples # Print the supported API Resources kubedb api-resources # Print the supported API Resources with more information kubedb api-resources -o wide # Print the supported namespaced resources kubedb api-resources --namespaced=true # Print the supported non-namespaced resources kubedb api-resources --namespaced=false # Print the supported API Resources with specific APIGroup kubedb api-resources --api-group=extensions Options --cached Use the cached list of resources if available.</description></item><item><title>Kubedb Create</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/kubedb_create/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/kubedb_create/</guid><description>kubedb create Create a resource from a file or from stdin.
Synopsis Create a resource from a file or from stdin.
JSON and YAML formats are accepted.
kubedb create -f FILENAME Examples # Create a elasticsearch using the data in elastic.json. kubedb create -f ./elastic.json # Create a elasticsearch based on the JSON passed into stdin. cat elastic.json | kubedb create -f - Options --allow-missing-template-keys If true, ignore any errors in templates when a field or map key is missing in the template.</description></item><item><title>Kubedb Delete</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/kubedb_delete/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/kubedb_delete/</guid><description>kubedb delete Delete resources by filenames, stdin, resources and names, or by resources and label selector
Synopsis Delete resources by filenames, stdin, resources and names, or by resources and label selector. JSON and YAML formats are accepted.
Note that the delete command does NOT do resource version checks
kubedb delete ([-f FILENAME] | TYPE [(NAME | -l label | --all)]) Examples # Delete a elasticsearch using the type and name specified in elastic.</description></item><item><title>Kubedb Describe</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/kubedb_describe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/kubedb_describe/</guid><description>kubedb describe Show details of a specific resource or group of resources
Synopsis Show details of a specific resource or group of resources. This command joins many API calls together to form a detailed description of a given resource or group of resources.
Use &amp;ldquo;kubedb api-resources&amp;rdquo; for a complete list of supported resources.
kubedb describe (-f FILENAME | TYPE [NAME_PREFIX | -l label] | TYPE/NAME) Examples # Describe a elasticsearch kubedb describe elasticsearches elasticsearch-demo # Describe a postgres kubedb describe pg/postgres-demo # Describe all dormantdatabases kubedb describe drmn Valid resource types include: * all * etcds * elasticsearches * postgreses * mysqls * mongodbs * redises * memcacheds * snapshots * dormantdatabases Options --all-namespaces If present, list the requested object(s) across all namespaces.</description></item><item><title>Kubedb Edit</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/kubedb_edit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/kubedb_edit/</guid><description>kubedb edit Edit a resource on the server
Synopsis Edit a resource from the default editor.
The edit command allows you to directly edit any API resource you can retrieve via the command line tools. It will open the editor defined by your KUBEDB _EDITOR, or EDITOR environment variables, or fall back to &amp;lsquo;nano&amp;rsquo;
kubedb edit (RESOURCE/NAME | -f FILENAME) Examples # Edit the elasticsearch named &#39;elasticsearch-demo&#39;: kubedb edit es/elasticsearch-demo # Use an alternative editor KUBEDB_EDITOR=&amp;quot;nano&amp;quot; kubedb edit es/elasticsearch-demo Options --allow-missing-template-keys If true, ignore any errors in templates when a field or map key is missing in the template.</description></item><item><title>Kubedb Get</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/kubedb_get/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/kubedb_get/</guid><description>kubedb get Display one or many resources
Synopsis Display one or many resources.
Use &amp;ldquo;kubedb api-resources&amp;rdquo; for a complete list of supported resources.
kubedb get [(-o|--output=)json|yaml|wide|custom-columns=...|custom-columns-file=...|go-template=...|go-template-file=...|jsonpath=...|jsonpath-file=...] (TYPE[.VERSION][.GROUP] [NAME | -l label] | TYPE[.VERSION][.GROUP]/NAME ...) [flags] Examples # List all elasticsearch in ps output format. kubedb get es # List all elasticsearch in ps output format with more information (such as version). kubedb get elasticsearches -o wide # List a single postgres with specified NAME in ps output format.</description></item><item><title>Kubedb Version</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/kubedb_version/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.1/reference/kubedb_version/</guid><description>kubedb version Prints binary version number.
Synopsis Prints binary version number.
kubedb version [flags] Options -h, --help help for version --short Print just the version number. Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups.</description></item></channel></rss>