<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Supported Databases | KubeDB on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/concepts/databases/</link><description>Recent content in Supported Databases | KubeDB on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/concepts/databases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Elasticsearch</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/concepts/databases/elasticsearch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/concepts/databases/elasticsearch/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Elasticsearch What is Elasticsearch Elasticsearch is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definitions (CRD). It provides declarative configuration for Elasticsearch in a Kubernetes native way. You only need to describe the desired database configuration in an Elasticsearch object, and the KubeDB operator will create Kubernetes objects in the desired state for you.
Elasticsearch Spec As with all other Kubernetes objects, an Elasticsearch needs apiVersion, kind, and metadata fields.</description></item><item><title>Memcached</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/concepts/databases/memcached/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/concepts/databases/memcached/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Memcached What is Memcached Memcached is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definitions (CRD). It provides declarative configuration for Memcached in a Kubernetes native way. You only need to describe the desired database configuration in a Memcached object, and the KubeDB operator will create Kubernetes objects in the desired state for you.
Memcached Spec As with all other Kubernetes objects, a Memcached needs apiVersion, kind, and metadata fields.</description></item><item><title>MongoDB</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/concepts/databases/mongodb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/concepts/databases/mongodb/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
MongoDB What is MongoDB MongoDB is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definitions (CRD). It provides declarative configuration for MongoDB in a Kubernetes native way. You only need to describe the desired database configuration in a MongoDB object, and the KubeDB operator will create Kubernetes objects in the desired state for you.
MongoDB Spec As with all other Kubernetes objects, a MongoDB needs apiVersion, kind, and metadata fields.</description></item><item><title>MySQL</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/concepts/databases/mysql/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/concepts/databases/mysql/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
MySQL What is MySQL MySQL is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definitions (CRD). It provides declarative configuration for MySQL in a Kubernetes native way. You only need to describe the desired database configuration in a MySQL object, and the KubeDB operator will create Kubernetes objects in the desired state for you.
MySQL Spec As with all other Kubernetes objects, a MySQL needs apiVersion, kind, and metadata fields.</description></item><item><title>Postgres</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/concepts/databases/postgres/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/concepts/databases/postgres/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Postgres What is Postgres Postgres is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definitions (CRD). It provides declarative configuration for PostgreSQL in a Kubernetes native way. You only need to describe the desired database configuration in a Postgres object, and the KubeDB operator will create Kubernetes objects in the desired state for you.
Postgres Spec As with all other Kubernetes objects, a Postgres needs apiVersion, kind, and metadata fields.</description></item><item><title>Redis</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/concepts/databases/redis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.9.0-rc.2/concepts/databases/redis/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Redis What is Redis Redis is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definitions (CRD). It provides declarative configuration for Redis in a Kubernetes native way. You only need to describe the desired database configuration in a Redis object, and the KubeDB operator will create Kubernetes objects in the desired state for you.
Redis Spec As with all other Kubernetes objects, a Redis needs apiVersion, kind, and metadata fields.</description></item></channel></rss>