<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Developer Guide on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/setup/developer-guide/</link><description>Recent content in Developer Guide on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/setup/developer-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Developer Guide</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/setup/developer-guide/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/setup/developer-guide/overview/</guid><description>Development Guide This document is intended to be the canonical source of truth for things like supported toolchain versions for building KubeDB. If you find a requirement that this doc does not capture, please submit an issue on github.
This document is intended to be relative to the branch in which it is found. It is guaranteed that requirements will change over time for the development branch, but release branches of KubeDB should not change.</description></item><item><title>Release</title><link>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/setup/developer-guide/release/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb-v2-hugo.web.app/docs/0.8.0-beta.2/setup/developer-guide/release/</guid><description>Release Process apimachinery Make sure apimachinery master builds and create a release-* branch.
apimachinery (master) $ ./hack/make.py Downloading: https://raw.githubusercontent.com/appscode/libbuild/master/libbuild.py Using existing version: github.appscode.libbuild.libbuild Ungrouping imports of dir: api Ungrouping imports of dir: client Ungrouping imports of dir: pkg goimports -w api client pkg gofmt -s -w api client pkg go build ./pkg/... ./api/... ./client/... apimachinery (master) $ git checkout release-0.1 Switched to branch &#39;release-0.1&#39; apimachinery (release-0.1) $ git merge master postgres Change the apimachinery dependency to release-* branch Revendor glide slow Make sure master branch compiles, commit any changes due to vendoring &amp;amp; push to origin master</description></item></channel></rss>