<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Elasticsearch Concepts on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.17/guides/elasticsearch/concepts/</link><description>Recent content in Elasticsearch Concepts on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.17/guides/elasticsearch/concepts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AppBinding CRD</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.17/guides/elasticsearch/concepts/appbinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.17/guides/elasticsearch/concepts/appbinding/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
AppBinding What is AppBinding An AppBinding is a Kubernetes CustomResourceDefinition(CRD) which points to an application using either its URL (usually for a non-Kubernetes resident service instance) or a Kubernetes service object (if self-hosted in a Kubernetes cluster), some optional parameters and a credential secret. To learn more about AppBinding and the problems it solves, please read this blog post: The case for AppBinding.</description></item><item><title>Elasticsearch CRD</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.17/guides/elasticsearch/concepts/elasticsearch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.17/guides/elasticsearch/concepts/elasticsearch/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
Elasticsearch What is Elasticsearch Elasticsearch is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definitions (CRD). It provides a declarative configuration for Elasticsearch in a Kubernetes native way. You only need to describe the desired database configuration in an Elasticsearch object, and the KubeDB operator will create Kubernetes objects in the desired state for you.
Elasticsearch Spec As with all other Kubernetes objects, an Elasticsearch needs apiVersion, kind, and metadata fields.</description></item><item><title>ElasticsearchAutoscaler CRD</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.17/guides/elasticsearch/concepts/autoscaler/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.17/guides/elasticsearch/concepts/autoscaler/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. ElasticsearchAutoscaler What is ElasticsearchAutoscaler ElasticsearchAutoscaler is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definitions (CRD). It provides a declarative configuration for autoscaling Elasticsearch compute resources and storage of database components in a Kubernetes native way.
ElasticsearchAutoscaler CRD Specifications Like any official Kubernetes resource, a ElasticsearchAutoscaler has TypeMeta, ObjectMeta, Spec and Status sections.</description></item><item><title>ElasticsearchOpsRequests CRD</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.17/guides/elasticsearch/concepts/elasticsearch-ops-request/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.17/guides/elasticsearch/concepts/elasticsearch-ops-request/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. ElasticsearchOpsRequest What is ElasticsearchOpsRequest ElasticsearchOpsRequest is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definitions (CRD). It provides a declarative configuration for the Elasticsearch administrative operations like database version upgrading, horizontal scaling, vertical scaling, etc. in a Kubernetes native way.
ElasticsearchOpsRequest Specifications Like any official Kubernetes resource, a ElasticsearchOpsRequest has TypeMeta, ObjectMeta, Spec and Status sections.</description></item><item><title>ElasticsearchVersion CRD</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.17/guides/elasticsearch/concepts/catalog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.17/guides/elasticsearch/concepts/catalog/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
ElasticsearchVersion What is ElasticsearchVersion ElasticsearchVersion is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definitions (CRD). It provides a declarative configuration to specify the docker images to be used for Elasticsearch database deployed with KubeDB in a Kubernetes native way.
When you install KubeDB, an ElasticsearchVersion custom resource will be created automatically for every supported Elasticsearch version. You have to specify the name of ElasticsearchVersion CRD in spec.</description></item></channel></rss>