<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Upgrading Redis on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/redis/upgrading/</link><description>Recent content in Upgrading Redis on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/redis/upgrading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Upgrading Redis Cluster</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/redis/upgrading/cluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/redis/upgrading/cluster/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Upgrade version of Redis Cluster This guide will show you how to use KubeDB Enterprise operator to upgrade the version of Redis cluster.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item><item><title>Upgrading Redis Overview</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/redis/upgrading/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/redis/upgrading/overview/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Upgrading Redis version Overview This guide will give you an overview on how KubeDB Enterprise operator upgrade the version of Redis database.
Before You Begin You should be familiar with the following KubeDB concepts: Redis RedisOpsRequest How Upgrade Process Works The following diagram shows how KubeDB Enterprise operator used to upgrade the version of Redis.</description></item><item><title>Upgrading Redis Standalone</title><link>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/redis/upgrading/standalone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedb.com/docs/v2021.03.11/guides/redis/upgrading/standalone/</guid><description>New to KubeDB? Please start here.
This is an Enterprise-only feature. Please install KubeDB Enterprise Edition to try this feature. Upgrade version of Redis Standalone This guide will show you how to use KubeDB Enterprise operator to upgrade the version of Redis standalone.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description></item></channel></rss>